<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-15"?>
<!-- * encoding is needed for selecting the correct code table               -->
<!--       iso-8859-5  : Cyrillic languages                                  -->
<!--       iso-8859-15 : western European languages                          -->
<!-- * The English attributes are not needed. They are not interpreted.      -->
<!-- * The "%s" is a placeholder for another part of the text.               -->
<!-- * "\n" indicates a new line. The game will add additinal line feeds, if -->
<!--   they are needed.                                                      -->
<!-- * All other line feeds within a text block will be replaced by a single -->
<!--   blank.                                                                -->
<MAX_Language_File lang="eng" encoding="iso-8859-15" direction="left-to-right">
	<Header>
		<Author name="JCK">
			<Editor name="JCK" time="2007-09-30 13:04:00"/>
			<Editor name="Someone" time="2007-09-30 13:04:00"/>
		</Author>
		<Game_Version time="2007-09-30 13:04:00"/>
	</Header>
	<Text>
		<Main>
			<Game_Title ENG="M.A.X."/>
			<Game_Subtitle ENG="Mechanized Assault and Exploration (TM)"/>
			<Version ENG="version v%s"/>
			<Credits_MM ENG="Michael Mönch's M.A.X. (Original by Interplay)"/>
			<Credits_Doc ENG="Michael Mönch's M.A.X. (Remake by DoctorDeath)"/>
			<Credits_Reloaded ENG="M.A.X. Reloaded based on Interplay's Mechanized Assault and Exploration"/>
			<Remarks>
				<Not_yet_implemented ENG="(*) not yet implemented"/>
			</Remarks>
		</Main>
		<Initialisation>
			<Load_Lang ENG="Loading languagepack..."/>
			<Load_Keys ENG="Loading keys..."/>
			<Load_Fonts ENG="Loading fonts..."/>
			<Load_GFX ENG="Loading gfx..."/>
			<Load_Effects ENG="Loading effects..."/>
			<Load_Terrain ENG="Loading terrain..."/>
			<Load_Vehicles ENG="Loading vehicles..."/>
			<Load_Buildings ENG="Loading buildings..."/>
			<Load_Music ENG="Loading music..."/>
			<Load_Sounds ENG="Loading sounds..."/>
			<Load_Voices ENG="Loading voices..."/>
		</Initialisation>
		<Menu_Main>
			<Title_Main_Menu ENG="Main Menu"/>
			<Button_Single_Player ENG="Singleplayer"/>
			<Button_Multi_Player ENG="Multiplayer"/>
			<Button_Map_Editor ENG="Mapeditor (*)"/>
			<Button_Credits ENG="Credits (*)"/>
			<Button_Mani ENG="Manifestation"/>
			<Button_Exit ENG="Exit"/>
			<Button_Back ENG="Back"/>
			<Button_OK ENG="OK"/>
			<Button_Yes ENG="Yes"/>
			<Button_No ENG="No"/>
			<Button_TCPIP_Host ENG="TCP/IP Host"/>
			<Button_TCPIP_Client ENG="TCP/IP Client"/>
			<Button_HotSeat_New ENG="New Hot Seat"/>
			<Button_HotSeat_Load ENG="Load Hot Seat"/>
			<Button_Game_New ENG="New Game"/>
			<Button_Game_Load ENG="Load Game"/>
			<Button_Game_Save ENG="Save Game"/>
			<Button_Game_Options ENG="Game Options"/>
			<Button_Load ENG="Load"/>
			<Button_Save ENG="Save"/>
			<Button_Training ENG="Training"/>
		</Menu_Main>
		<Game_Options>
			<Title_Credits ENG="Credits"/>
			<Title_Gold ENG="Gold"/>
			<Title_Metal ENG="Metal"/>
			<Title_Oil ENG="Oil"/>
			<Title_BridgeHead ENG="Bridgehead"/>
			<Title_Alien_Tech ENG="Alientechnology"/>
			<Title_Resource ENG="Resources"/>
			<Title_Resource_Density ENG="Resources Density"/>
			<Title_Game_Type ENG="Game Type"/>
			<Option_Lowest ENG="lowest"/>
			<Option_Lower ENG="very low"/>
			<Option_Low ENG="low"/>
			<Option_Normal ENG="normal"/>
			<Option_Much ENG="much"/>
			<Option_More ENG="very much"/>
			<Option_Most ENG="most"/>
			<Option_Thick ENG="thick"/>
			<Option_Thin ENG="thin"/>
			<Option_On ENG="on"/>
			<Option_Off ENG="off"/>
			<Option_Definite ENG="definite"/>
			<Option_Mobile ENG="mobile"/>
			<Option_Type_Turns ENG="turns"/>
			<Option_Type_Simu ENG="simultaneous"/>
		</Game_Options>
		<Game_Settings>
			<Title_Preferences ENG="Preferences"/>
			<Title_Volume ENG="Volume"/>
			<Title_Music ENG="Music"/>
			<Title_Effects ENG="Effects"/>
			<Title_Voices ENG="Voices"/>
			<Title_Disable ENG="Disable"/>
			<Title_Scrollspeed ENG="Scrollspeed"/>
			<Title_Autosave ENG="Autosave"/>
			<Title_Animation ENG="Animations"/>
			<Title_Alphaeffects ENG="Alphaeffects"/>
			<Title_Shadows ENG="Shadows"/>
			<Title_ShowDamage ENG="Buildingdamage"/>
			<Title_ShowDamageVehicle ENG="Vehicledamage"/>
			<Title_Tracks ENG="Vehicletracks"/>
		</Game_Settings>
		<Game_Start>
			<Title_Player_Name ENG="Playername:"/>
			<Title_Player_Select ENG="Playeroptions"/>
			<Title_Team ENG="Team"/>
			<Title_Human ENG="Human"/>
			<Title_Computer ENG="Computer"/>
			<Title_Nobody ENG="Nobody"/>
			<Title_Clan ENG="Clan"/>
			<Title_Cargo ENG="Cargo"/>
			<Title_Choose_Planet ENG="Planetchoosing"/>
			<Title_Options ENG="Options"/>
			<Title_Connect ENG="Connect"/>
			<Title_Send ENG="Send"/>
			<Title_Color ENG="Color:"/>
			<Title_IP ENG="IP"/>
			<Title_Port ENG="Port"/>
			<Title_Map ENG="Map"/>
			<Title_LoadSave ENG="Load/Save Menu"/>
			<Title_Load ENG="Load Menu"/>
			<Button_Host_Start ENG="Start Host"/>
		</Game_Start>
		<Game_MP>
			<Title_Player ENG="Player"/>
			<Comp_Waiting ENG="Waiting for other players..."/>
			<Comp_Player_Few ENG="Not enough players!"/>
			<Comp_Player_Many ENG="Too many players!"/>
			<Comp_Player_Twice ENG="Playername exists twice: "/>
			<Comp_Player_Wrong ENG="Missing a correct player's name"/>
			<Comp_Player_MustHost ENG="must be host in turnbased game!"/>
			<Comp_Player_Amount ENG="Amount of players:"/>
			<Comp_Player_Turn ENG="'s turn"/>
			<Comp_Network_Error_Socket ENG="Error opening socket"/>
			<Comp_Network_Error_Connect ENG="Could not connect to "/>
			<Comp_Network_Open ENG="Game open"/>
			<Comp_Network_Connecting ENG="Connecting to "/>
			<Comp_Network_New ENG="New connection"/>
			<Comp_Network_Connected ENG="Connected"/>
			<Comp_Network_Connected_Not ENG="Not connected"/>
			<Comp_Network_Closed ENG="Connection closed"/>
			<Comp_Map_NoSet ENG="--no map set--"/>
			<Comp_Option_NoSet ENG="--no options set--"/>
			<Comp_Go ENG="Let's go"/>
			<Comp_Go_Abort ENG="Go aborted"/>
			<Comp_Go_Host ENG="Host wants to go: Ready to go"/>
			<Comp_Go_Host_No ENG="Host wants to go: No go"/>
			<Comp_Go_Ready ENG="Ready to go"/>
			<Comp_Go_Ready_No ENG="not ready to go"/>
			<Comp_Go_Check ENG="Check for go"/>
		</Game_MP>
		<Vehicles>
			<Title_Damage ENG="Damage"/>
			<Title_Shoots ENG="Shoots"/>
			<Title_Range ENG="Range"/>
			<Title_Ammo ENG="Ammo"/>
			<Title_Armor ENG="Armor"/>
			<Title_Hitpoints ENG="Hitpoints"/>
			<Title_Scan ENG="Scan"/>
			<Title_Speed ENG="Speed"/>
		</Vehicles>
		<Comp>
			<Fuel_Low ENG="To low fuel, generator disabled!"/>
			<Energy_Low ENG="To low energy, disabled consumer!"/>
			<Metal_Low ENG="To low metal, disabled consumer!"/>
			<Gold_Low ENG="To low gold, disabled consumer!"/>
			<Team_Low ENG="To low teams, disabled consumer!"/>
			<Energy_Optimize ENG="Energygeneration optimized"/>
			<Cheat ENG="used cheat"/>
			<Destroyed ENG="destroyed"/>
			<Defeated ENG="defeated"/>
			<Finished ENG="is finished"/>
			<Finished2 ENG="are finished"/>
			<Detected ENG="detected"/>
			<Attacked ENG="is under attack"/>
			<End_Game ENG="Exit really?\n\nNot saved gamedata will be lost."/>
			<Turn_Start ENG="Start turn"/>
			<Turn_Wait ENG="Please wait until all movements are completed"/>
			<Turn_Automove ENG="Executing remaining movements"/>
			<Research_Attack ENG="Research 'Attack' completed"/>
			<Research_Shoots ENG="Research 'Shoots' completed"/>
			<Research_Range ENG="Research 'Range' completed"/>
			<Research_Armor ENG="Research 'Armor' completed"/>
			<Research_Hitpoints ENG="Research 'Hitpoints' completed"/>
			<Research_Speed ENG="Research 'Speed' completed"/>
			<Research_Scan ENG="Research 'Scan' completed"/>
			<Research_Costs ENG="Research 'Costs' completed"/>
		</Comp>
		<Error_Messages>
			<ERROR_File_Not_Found ENG="File not found: %s"/>
			<ERROR_Missing_Translation ENG="missing translation: %s"/>
			<ERROR_Map_Loading ENG="Error loading map"/>
			<INFO_Language_initialised ENG="Language is now initialised"/>
			<INFO_Not_Implemented ENG="Not yet implemented"/>
		</Error_Messages>
	</Text>
	<Units>
		<Unit ID="0 1" ENG="Air Transport">Air Transport\n\nHeavy aircraft capable of holding up to three ground units.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="0 2" ENG="Alien Assault">Alien Assault\n\nPowerful plasma weapon mounted on a fast, medium-armored chassis. While not as fragile as human assault gunns, the alien assault gun should still avoid enemy fire whenever possible. All alien unitsrepair themselves, and improve their abilities with experience.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="0 3" ENG="Alien Plane">Alien Plane\n\nAlien fighter-bomber. While the alien plane is primarily desinged to attack ground targets, it can also fire its missiles at other planes. Though powerful, the alien attack plane is still vulnerable to anti aircraft fire. Like other alien units, alien planes repair themselves and improve their abilities wity experience.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="0 4" ENG="Alien Ship">Alien Ship\n\nHeavily armored and armed warship of alien design. Like the human gunboat, the alien gunboat excels at destroying other ships and land targets near the shore. All alien units repair themselves, and improve their abilities with experience.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="0 5" ENG="Alien Tank">Alien Tank\n\nHeavily armored tank of alien design. Alien tanks are best used at the front of an attack to soak up enemy fire. All alien units repair themselves, and improve their abilities with erperience.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="0 6" ENG="Personnel Carrier">Personnel Carrier\n\nFast armored vehicle to transport infantery and infiltrators. Tha APC can move slowly underwater as well es on land. Only enemy corvettes can detect an APC moving under water.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="0 7" ENG="Assault Gun">Assault Gun\n\nLightly armored vehicle with a long range gun firing high-explosive shells. Fast and effective on the attack, but fragile.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="0 8" ENG="AWAC">AWAC\n\nAirborne Warning And Control plane. Basically a flying radar dish, an AWAC is essential to spot enemy anti aircraft before your planes fly info firing range.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="0 9" ENG="Ground Attack Plane">Ground Attack Plane\n\nA hevier plane carrying a full load of air to ground missiles. Ground Attack Planes are expencive, but the advantages are worth the cost. Their great speet lets them reach any trouble spot quickly, and once they arrive, only fighters and antiaircraft can defend against them.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="0 10" ENG="Bulldozer">Bulldozer\n\nVehicle for clearing rubble and demolishing buildings. Bulldozers can scavenge material from debris.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="0 11" ENG="Cargo Ship">Cargo Ship\n\nShips for hauling raw material. Useful for resupplying pioneers and sea combat units with new ammunition.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="0 12" ENG="Rocket Launcher">Rocket Launcher\n\nLightly armored vehicle firing medium-range rockets which affect all units within 2 squares of the target. Most effective against groups of enemy units.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="0 13" ENG="Infiltrator">Infiltrator\n\nCommando trained in the arts of stealth and electronic warfare. Infiltrators can disable or capture enemy units. Infiltrators are normally invisible until they make a mistake trying to capture enemy units, or until spotted by infantery or infiltrators.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="0 14" ENG="Corvette">Corvette\n\nHigh speed boat with torpedo tubes and sonar. Corvettes can attack any sea unit, but their real strength is their ability to spot and attack submarines.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="0 15" ENG="Escort">Escort\n\nHigh speed boat with good radar and rapid fire anti aircraft cannon. Escorts are the eyes of a fleet, and a fleet's protection from planes.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="0 16" ENG="Fighter">Fighter\n\nFast but fragile aircraft carrying a limited number of air-to-air missiles. Fighters are the best way to drive enemy planes out an area, and to defend a moving force. Ground based anti aircraft is a better choice for defending a fixed area.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="0 17" ENG="Gunboat">Gunboat\n\nHeavily armored ship with a high caliber, medium range cannon. Excellent at destroying other ships and bombing shore targets.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="0 18" ENG="Infantery">Infantery\n\nHuman soldiers equipped with light anti-tank shoulder weapons. Infantery can spot enemy infiltrators.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="0 19" ENG="Constructor">Constructor\n\nLarge construction vehicle for creating large buildings, such as mines and factories. A constructor consumes two materials per turn while operating.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="0 20" ENG="Mine Layer">Mine Layer\n\nMinelayers are specialized construction vehicles which place, detect, and remove mines. Minelayers convert onboard raw materials into mines. They can also remove those mines later and convert them back into materials. They cannot remove enemy minefields - those must be exploded with gunfire and rockets.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="0 21" ENG="Missile Crawler">Missile Crawler\n\nMissile launcher on an lightly armored chassis. This mobile launcher is slightly less sturdy than the stationary version, and requires more material tu build. However, the ability to move makes it much more flexible.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="0 22" ENG="Missile Cruiser">Missile Cruiser\n\nShip mounted missile launcher. Excellent range, high attack strength, and medium armor makes this a powerful unit.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="0 23" ENG="Mobile Anti Aircraft">Mobile Anti Aircraft\n\nLight, fast vehicle with a rapid fire cannon for shooting down enemy planes. Mobile anti aircraft are generally defensive units, because they aren't as fast as planes, and can't move while firing. Use them to protect an area once your fighters have chased away enemy ground attack planes.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="0 24" ENG="Pioneer">Small construktion vehical for creating small buildings and stationary weapons.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="0 25" ENG="Repair Unit">Repair Unit\n\nLight vehicle which can rapidly repair ground units and buildings. Repairs require materials. The most extensive the damage, the more materials the repair requires. Depots, docks, hangars and barracks can also repair units.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="0 26" ENG="Scanner">Scanner\n\nMobile radar platform. Slower and more expensive than a scout, but with a better scan range. A scanner is an excellent way to spot targets for very long ranged units like missile crawlers.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="0 27" ENG="Scout">Scout\n\nHigh speed scouting vehical for exploration and spotting enemy units. Can cross water without a bridge, but is faster an land.\n\nVery fast and good scan range, but much weaker than most combat units.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="0 28" ENG="Sea Mine Layer">Sea Mine Layer\n\nSeaborne version of the minelayer. Like its land based counterpart, the sea minelayer can manufracture mines, detect them, and convert them back into raw material.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="0 29" ENG="Sea Transport">Sea Transport\n\nHeavily armored ship with space to carry up to six land units. Sea transports are much slower than air transports, but also much more likely to survive an enemy attack.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="0 30" ENG="Submarine">Submarine\n\nLurking beneath the surface, submarines can sneak close to the enemy to fire their powerful torpedoes. Submarines do not carry active sonar, which might reveal their positions. Only corvettes can spot a submarine before it fires. Only submarines, corvettes, and ground attack planes can attack them.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="0 31" ENG="Surveyor">Surveyor\n\nLight, amphibious vehicle with sophisticated sensors for detecting underground minerals and enemy mines. Unlike most amphibious units, surveyors are just as fast on water an on Land.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="0 32" ENG="Tank">Tank\n\nHeavily armored fighting vehical. Best used in the frontline to prevent enemy units from reaching lightly-armored support units such as assult guns and rocket launchers.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="0 33" ENG="Gold Truck">Gold Truck\n\nUnit for moving gold ore from one location to another.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="0 34" ENG="Supply Truck">Supply Truck\n\nTruck for hauling raw materials. Useful for resupplying pioneers and constructors, and for supplying combat units with new ammunition.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="0 35" ENG="Fuel Truck">Fuel Truck\n\nTruck for moving fuel.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="1 1" ENG="Barracks">Barracks\n\nA barracks holds infiltrators and infantery units. Inside the barracks is a machine shop for repairing and improving powered suits, and for manufacturing ammunition. The barracks needs raw materials to repair, upgrade or resupply, so it should be connected to a storage unit or a minig station.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="1 2" ENG="Concrete Block">Concrete Block\n\nHardened, armored block for blocking enemy movement.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="1 3" ENG="Bridge">Bridge\n\nPontoon bridge for crossing water. Bridges, unlike water platforms, do not block the movement of ships.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="1 4" ENG="Connector">Connector\n\nBuildings must be connected to share power, fuel, raw materials and gold. You can connect buildings by placing them next to each other, or by building connectors from one building to the other.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="1 5" ENG="Depot">Depot\n\nA depot can repair damage, manufracture ammunition, and refit ground units with the newest technology. All of these operations require raw materials, so depots should be connected to stored materials.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="1 6" ENG="Dock">Dock\n\nA dock can repair damage, manufacture ammunition and refit ships with the newest technology. All of these operations require raw materials, so docks should be connected to stored materials.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="1 7" ENG="Power Station">Power Station\n\nA power station consumes six fuel each turn, and provides enough power for six factories or mining stations.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="1 8" ENG="Power Generator">Power Generator\n\nA power generator consumes two fuel each turn, and provides enough power for one mining station or factory. The power generator must be connected to the fuel source (minig station or fuel tank) and the building that needs the power.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="1 9" ENG="Air Units Plant">Air Units Plant\n\nBuilds fighters, ground attack planes, AWACs and air transports. A air units plant needs three raw materials a turn to operate and power.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="1 10" ENG="Alien Units Plant">Alien Units Plant</Unit>
		<Unit ID="1 11" ENG="Heavy Vehicle Plant">Heavy Vehicle Plant\n\nBuilds construtors, mobile scanners, and the heavy fighting units: tanks, assult guns, rocket launchers and missile crawlers. A heavy vehicle factory needs three raw materials a turn to operate, and power.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="1 12" ENG="Shipyard">Shipyard\n\nShipyards manufacture ships, such as submarines, sea transporters and missile cruisers. A shipyard requires three raw materials a turn to operate, an power.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="1 13" ENG="Light Vehicle Plant">Light Vehicle Plant\n\nBuilds light vehicles: pioneers, trucks, mobile repair units, scouts and mobile anti-aircraft units. A light vehicle plant requires three raw materials a turn to operate, and power from a power generator or power station.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="1 14" ENG="Gold Refinery">Gold Refinery\n\nRefinery for converting gold into credits. Credits are required to purchase unit improvements. To run, a gold refinery needs a source of gold ore. A mining station can produce gold ore if one of its four spuares covers a spuare with undergound gold.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="1 15" ENG="Anti Aircraft">Anti Aircraft\n\nLow caliber, high speed anti aircraft cannon. Anti aircraft make short work of planes, but cannot attack ground units.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="1 16" ENG="Artillery">Artillery\n\nHigh powered stationary gun. Artillery is a compromise between the cheap, rugged gun turret and the expensive, long-range missile turret.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="1 17" ENG="Missile Launcher">Missile Launcher\n\nLong-range missile launcher on a fixed mount. Exellent range and firepower, but only slightly more armor than the mobile version. Best surrounded by gun turrets and anti aircraft.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="1 18" ENG="Gun Turret">Gun Turret\n\nHeavily armored stationary gun turret. Gun turrets have good firepower, heavy armor, and moderate range. Because they take little time to build, they are a good choice when you need defense in a hurry.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="1 19" ENG="Habitat">Habitat\n\nHabitats house colonists. Each habitat houses enough colonists to operate three research centers, training halls or eco-spheres. The colonist buildings must be connected to the habitat befor they can operate.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="1 20" ENG="Hangar">Hangar\n\nA hangar can repair damage, manufracture ammunition and refit planes with the newest technology. All of these operations require raw materials, so hangars should be connected to stored materials.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="1 21" ENG="Land Mine">Land Mine\n\nSmall, hard to detect explosive device. Only surveyors, minelayers, and infiltratoers can spot mines. Once spotted, almost any damage will destroy it.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="1 22" ENG="Mining Station">Mining Station\n\nExtracts raw materials, fuel and gold from the ground everuy turn. Buildings must be connected to a mine to use the resources a mine produces. If there are no storage buildings, to store extra materials, it will be lost.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="1 23" ENG="Deep Mine">Deep Mine...</Unit>
		<Unit ID="1 24" ENG="Landing Pad">Landing Pad\n\nLanding facility for planes. Does not repair, resupply or refuel planes. To resupply a plane on a landing pad, use a nearby truck or storage unit.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="1 25" ENG="Water Platform">Water Platform\n\nProvides a surface over water on which to construct other buildings. Pioneers can build water platforms over the shore as well as open water. Water platforms are particularly important an island maps, or when a valuable material deposit is under water.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="1 26" ENG="Radar">Radar\n\nStationary, long-range radar. Longer-range units like missile launchers and artillery cannot fire on what thay cannot see, so it's important to have a scanner or radar nearby.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="1 27" ENG="Research Center">Research Center\n\nResearch centers investigate ways to improve your units. Unlike upgrades purcased with refined gold, research takes time, and the improvements are small. Hovever, research affects all of your units instead of just one type, and doesn't require a source of gold ore. A research center requires colonists from a habitat to operate, and power.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="1 28" ENG="Road">Road\n\nUnits move twice as fast over road spuares.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="1 29" ENG="Sea Mine">Sea Mine\n\nSmall, hard to detect explosive device. Only surveyors, minelayers, and infiltratoers can spot mines. Once spotted, almost any damage will destroy it.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="1 30" ENG="Shield">Shield</Unit>
		<Unit ID="1 31" ENG="Gold Vault">Gold Vault\n\nHolds unrefined gold ore. Minig stations produce gold every turn, if they have gold ore underneath them. To store the ore, a mining station must be connected to a gold vault.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="1 32" ENG="Storage Unit">Storage Unit\n\nHolds raw materials. Mining stations produce raw materials ervery turn. To save extra materials, a minig station must be connected to a storage unit.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="1 33" ENG="Fuel Tank">Fuel Tank\n\nHolds fuel reserves. Minig stations produce fuel every turn. To save extra fuel, a mining station must be connected to a fuel tank.</Unit>
		<Unit ID="1 34" ENG="Training Hall">Training Hall\n\nTrains infiltrators who can disable or capture enemy units, and infantry to guard against infiltrators. A training hall requires colonists from a habitat and power to operate.</Unit>
	</Units>
	<Graphic>
		<Dummy/>
	</Graphic>
	<Speech>
		<Dummy/>
	</Speech>
</MAX_Language_File>
